{
    "subject": "resource/Moolah_Beach",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:2001_American_television_series_debuts",
    "human_readable": "Moolah Beach is the subject of 2001 American television series debuts.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9538806080818176,
            "question": "What year did the American television series about Moolah Beach debut?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8566356301307678,
            "question": "In what country did the American television series about Moolah Beach premiere?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.833768367767334,
            "question": "Is there a television series based on Moolah Beach?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7941507697105408,
            "question": "How popular was the American television series about Moolah Beach?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7363898158073425,
            "question": "What is the main theme of the American television series about Moolah Beach?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7311843633651733,
            "question": "What nationality was the television series about Moolah Beach?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6251598000526428,
            "question": "What is Moolah Beach known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6188248991966248,
            "question": "Was there a popular film or television show set in Moolah Beach?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4983415901660919,
            "question": "What type of media features Moolah Beach?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4782804250717163,
            "question": "Can you name any actors who starred in the American television series about Moolah Beach?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Moolah Beach is the subject of 2001 American television series debuts.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3693_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of media features Moolah Beach?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3693_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was there a popular film or television show set in Moolah Beach?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3693_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Moolah Beach known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3693_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3693_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3693_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3693_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3693_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3693_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3693_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3693_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3693_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3693_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3693_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that while the documents mention various details about Moolah Beach, such as its air dates (9/8/2001 - 11/24/2001), filming dates (July 9\u201420, 2001), and number of episodes (13), there is no indication in the documents that Moolah Beach was a subject of a 2001 American television series debut. Therefore, the information does not support this triple."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the television series *Moolah Beach*, including its debut in 2001, making it clear that it is part of a 2001 American television series."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The context information clearly states that Moolah Beach premiered on September 8, 2001. This directly contradicts the idea that it is a subject of 2001 American television series debuts, implying that there were other shows premiering in 2001 as well.",
            "category": -1
        }
    }
}